Okay, tons of cool stuff just happened
and it's happened too fast. But let me
let me quickly recap what I just
happened. So, first of all, I used one
of the the pro tips that we went through
in week two, which is to press control O
to look at the full conversation to see
what was going on and to to satisfy
myself that indeed uh most of the tests
passed, some failed, and it correctly
accounted for that. So, that was a nice
thing to do. Next up, I asked it to push
its changes to GitHub, and that didn't
work because we're not logged into
GitHub here, and it told me you have to
log in to GitHub with ghorth login,
something that we just covered, I think,
yesterday. Uh, no, no, earlier today.
So, I I stopped cla
twice. I did gh login and it spawned a
window on my computer even though we're
in the in the cloud. I logged into
GitHub and then we were logged into
GitHub. I then typed Claude to go back
into Claude code but but the
conversation was started again from the
beginning and I just typed slashres and
remember from from the beginning of week
two that slashres just takes us back to
where we were and I could just say you
can see I said right here okay I've
logged you into GitHub please try now
and sure enough it made uh it it made a
it had already made a branch. It then
pushed that branch to GitHub and it told
me it's it's created a pull request and
this is now ready for my review on
GitHub. Let's go take a look. So here it
is. Here is the finally repo. There is
indeed a market data review. Let's
compare it. Let's take a look at it. Uh
here it is. It's got this market data
review.md.
There is all of the information
including some of the problems with it.
Uh and uh so let's say create a pull
request
and let's merge it.
Confirm the merge
and we are done. Fantastic. Well, now
I'm I'm I'm on a roll here. I'm enjoying
the fact that we're operating in the
cloud like this. And we can just keep
going. So I can say, okay, I've merged.
Please
uh switch
to mass domain and do a pull
and do a pull.
Then please um then then please uh carry
out
all the fixes and improvements
that you've documented
in the uh the review file.
Keep working
until all tests pass
and the product the market data
the market data back end is ready.
Then
uh push your new branch
to GitHub.
That's it. I'm running that. It's all
going to run in the cloud again on
sprites.dev in a YOLO world where it can
do whatever it wants because we know
we've got it nicely sandboxed. It's not
touching my computer. It can't do damage
to me. So, there we go. This is so
efficient because there's no more of
this permissions approval nonsense. It's
all running. It's going to do its thing
and uh I will check back in when we have
a working market data back end. And I
tell you, it's just been the most
amazing experience sitting here watching
this happening. I haven't approved
anything. It's been working and working,
fixing bugs one by one, rerunning the
tests, more are passing, reporting on
problems, and then at the end, it
created a branch. It's submitted the the
uh the the push, everything just
happening. Uh and uh it's yeah, it's
created the PR. It's ready for me to
review it. And I've got this sense that
it's super productive and lots are going
on, lots of things going on, and yet
it's also secure. It's happening in a
way that is totally sandboxed. So, it
really feels like I've got the best of
both, which is a great feeling. And I I
continued a conversation with Claude. I
gave it a bit of feedback on the changes
that I made. It made some more changes.
There's now a PR that's ready for me to
to review. Here we go.
And we're going to have the PR to merge
this in. and merge and confirm merge and
this is fixed and it also incorporated
the extra change I asked as well and so
everything is now included in
and it's all successfully done that is
finished uh so uh we we have
successfully carried out a bunch of work
in our remote sandbox courtesy of
sprites.dev dev. And one final point to
make on this is that you don't need to
just use this for claude. You could use
this of course for codecs, for open
code, for whichever one you have picked.
It is ideal for running in a sandbox
regardless of your platform. And with
that, that's enough for today to remind
you one more time the three different
approaches that we used today in blue.
The first thing we did is using the
built-in/ sandbox, which is a sort of
cheap and cheerful way of basically like
having your own Docker container. It's
like a lightweight OS level clawed
codebuilt sandboxing running on your
machine. We did that. It was easy. In
purple, this is where you take advantage
of anthropics remote running, remote
execution with with sandboxes built in.
And there's a bunch of different ways of
doing it. Some of them didn't work for
me, but but will be working by now. You
should try them. But one of the ones
some of the ones that did work was using
the web interface, using the mobile app,
which was cool. And then the coolest of
all was going to get GitHub, putting in
an issue. Uh it could also be like a PR
and then and tagging Claude and watching
it like pick up that issue, running it
in the anthropic remote box, and then
just just raising the change at the end
of it. Uh pushing its its branch.
Amazing. And then in yellow, after doing
all of that, we looked at a completely
different approach, which is when we
don't use Anthropic in the cloud. We use
a third party, in this case, the company
fly.io that has this this offering
sprites.dev. We use that. It's it's one
of the new ones that's that's really
fast, really easy to use, and it gives
you like a command line interface, which
is actually remoting into something
running on the cloud, but we could treat
it as if it was a my own machine. And it
was a bit confusing because I was
running it within VS Code. So it really
felt like it was on my machine and we
could interact with it. We could sign
into GitHub remotely. We could sign into
Claude and then we could carry out
activities and we could be in YOLO mode
running really efficiently but feeling
very secure as we did. And that was the
the final approach, the yellow approach
running on a third party cloud sandbox.
And so with that, I promised you a juicy
day. And hopefully you agree it was a
juicy day. Tomorrow, large code bases, a
big area of of concern from people when
they're working with coding agents. How
does it perform on a big codebase? We're
going to cover that. But also, I'm going
to throw some spicy stuff in the mix.
Going to spice it up tomorrow as you
will see. And then the going to be a
kind of crescendo because the day after
is all about the swarms and
orchestrators. That's that's all the
rage at the moment before we land on our
capstone. Okay, see you tomorrow. For
now, take a moment to wallow in the fact
that you are 80% through. 20% left to go
before you have really mastered coding
agents. See you tomorrow.